Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records Documenting Swimming
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records documenting swimming, 1899-1995; Accession 2006-A-056
  - Photographs
    - Unsigned Photographs
      - 1920-1929 (Box 18, Folder 514)
      - 1930-1939 (Box 18, Folder 515)
      - 1950-1959 (Box 18, Folder 516)
      - 1960-1969 (Box 18, Folder 517)
      - Art/drawings, undated (Box 18, Folder 518)
    - International Games/Olympics (Box 19)
    - Olympics, 1936 (Box 20)
    - Olympics, 1936 (Box 39)
    - Team Photographs
      - 1899-1910 (Box 21, Folder 519)
      - 1911-1920 (Box 21, Folder 520)
      - 1921-1930 (Box 21, Folder 521)
      - 1931-1940 (Box 21, Folder 522)
      - 1941-1950 (Box 21, Folder 523)
      - 1951-1960 (Box 21, Folder 524)
      - 1961-1970 (Box 21, Folder 525)
      - 1971-1980 (Box 21, Folder 526)
      - 1981-1992 (Box 21, Folder 527)
      - 2001-? (Box 21, Folder 528)
      - Undated (Box 21, Folder 529)
      - 1974-1982 (Women) (Box 21, Folder 530)
      - 1983-1992 (Women) (Box 21, Folder 531)
    - Unidentified swimming photographs (New Haven Swim Club?) (Box 22)
    - Yale/Non Yale
      - Yale individuals, 1960-1969 (Box 23, Folder 532)
      - Yale events, 1940-1949 (Box 23, Folder 533)
      - Training photographs, undated (Box 23, Folder 535)
      - Non-Yale individuals/groups, undated (Box 23, Folder 536)
      - Unidentified individuals/groups, undated (Box 23, Folder 537)
      - Unidentified meet, undated (Box 23, Folder 538)
    - Kiphuth family/personal photographs (Box 40)
  - Publications
    - International publications, 1953-1969 (Box 24, Folder 539)
    - International records, 1967-1972 (Box 24, Folder 540)
    - Lifeguarding regulations (Box 24, Folder 541)
    - Meet programmes, 1921-1995 (Box 24, Folder 542)
    - Miscellaneous fitness publications (Box 24, Folder 543)
    - National group publications, 1959-1971 (Box 24, Folder 544)
    - Swimming newsletters, 1958-1992 (Box 24, Folder 545)
    - Swimming periodicals, 1963-1967 (Box 24, Folder 546)
    - Swimming and water polo brochures, 1971-1998 (Box 24, Folder 547)
    - Yale swimming miscellaneous publications, 1921-1995 (Box 24, Folder 548)
  - Reports, 1922-1927 (Box 25, Folder 549 - 553)
  - Results
    - Team records, 1907-1944 (Box 26, Folder 554)
    - Varsity freestyle, 1932-1945 (Box 26, Folder 555)
    - Indoor AAU summaries, 1932-1957 (Box 26, Folder 556)
    - General results, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 557)
    - Meet results, 1933-1941 (Box 26, Folder 558)
    - Record times, 1934-1951 (Box 26, Folder 559)
    - AAU, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 560)
    - Swimmers' records, 1938-1939 (Box 26, Folder 561)
    - Swim meets, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 562)
    - EISL, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 563)
    - Swim meets, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 564)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 565)
    - Team statistics, 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 566)
    - Applications of records, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 567)
    - Varsity individuals, 1946-1951 (Box 26, Folder 568)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 569)
    - Keo Nakama swimming meet, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 570)
    - Women's Outdoor AAU, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 571)
    - EISL, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 572)
    - Swimmer statistics, 1949-1950 (Box 26A, Folder 1)
    - Swimming team records, 1949-1953 (Box 26, Folder 573)
    - Indoor AAU, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 574)
    - NCISA, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 575)
    - Swim meets, 1950-1952 (Box 26A, Folder 2)
    - 1950 Mar 31, Apr 1 (Box 26, Folder 576)
    - Indoor AAU, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 577)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 578)
    - Swim meets (Fordham, Navy, Penn, Army), 1951 (Box 26, Folder 579)
    - International results, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 580)
    - Indoor AAU, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 581)
    - EISL, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 582)
    - Varsity results, 1952-1953 (Box 26, Folder 583)
    - Freshman results, 1952-1953 (Box 26, Folder 584)
    - Indoor AAU, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 585)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 586)
    - Summaries, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 587)
    - Freshman results, 1953-1954 (Box 26, Folder 587a)
    - Varsity results, 1953-1954 (Box 26, Folder 588)
    - Indoor AAU, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 589)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 590)
    - NCAA Swimming Championships, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 591)
    - All American suggested, 1954-1955 (Box 26, Folder 592)
    - Freshman results, 1954-1955 (Box 26, Folder 593)
    - Varsity results, 1954-1955 (Box 26, Folder 594)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 595)
    - EISL, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 596 - 597)
    - NCAA Swimming Championships, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 598)
    - EISL Championships, 1954-1955 (Box 26, Folder 599)
    - Pan Am Games, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 600)
    - Pan Am tryouts, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 601)
    - AAU National Championships, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 602)
    - Championships summaries, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 603)
    - Unknown meet, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 604)
    - Freshman results, 1955-1956 (Box 27, Folder 605)
    - Championship results, 1955-1956 (Box 27, Folder 606)
    - Varsity results, 1955-1956 (Box 27, Folder 607)
    - Results, 1955-1958 (Box 27, Folder 608)
    - Indoor AAU, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 609)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 610)
    - EISL Swimming Championships, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 611)
    - NCAA Swimming Championships, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 612)
    - EISL, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 613)
    - Championship results, 1956-1957 (Box 27, Folder 614)
    - Freshman results, 1956-1957 (Box 27, Folder 615)
    - Freshmen, 1956-1957 (Box 27, Folder 616)
    - Varsity results, 1956-1957 (Box 27, Folder 617)
    - Indoor AAU, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 618)
    - Outdoor AAU (M), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 619)
    - Outdoor AAU (W), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 620)
    - EISL Swimming Championships, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 621)
    - NCAA Swimming Championships, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 622)
    - Varsity results, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 623 - 624)
    - Freshman results, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 625 - 627)
    - Varsity individuals, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 628)
    - Performance statistics, 1957-1960 (Box 27, Folder 629 - 631)
    - Performance statistics, 1957-1960 (Box 28, Folder 632 - 638)
    - AAU comparisons (Outdoor), 1957-1972 (Box 28, Folder 639)
    - AAU comparisons (Indoor), 1957-1972 (Box 28, Folder 640)
    - ECAC comparisons, 1957-1973 (Box 28, Folder 641)
    - NCAA comparisons, 1957-1973 (Box 28, Folder 642)
    - Indoor AAU, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 643)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 644)
    - EISL Swimming Championships, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 645)
    - NCAA Swimming Championships, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 646)
    - Freshman meet results, 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 647)
    - Varsity meet results, 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 648)
    - NCAA, 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 649)
    - Indoor AAU, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 650)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 651)
    - EISL, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 652)
    - EISL Championships, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 653)
    - NCAA Swimming Championships, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 654)
    - Pan Am tryouts, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 655)
    - Pan American Games, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 656 - 657)
    - U.S. vs. Japan 5th quadrennial dual meet, 1959 (Box 26A, Folder 3)
    - Freshman results, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 658)
    - Varsity results, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 659)
    - Indoor AAU, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 660)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 661)
    - EISL Swimming Championships, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 662)
    - NCAA Swimming Championships, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 663 - 665)
    - EISL, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 666)
    - Freshman individual, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 667)
    - Freshman meet results, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 668)
    - Varsity individual, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 669)
    - Varsity events, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 670)
    - Varsity results, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 671)
    - Indoor AAU, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 672)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 673)
    - NCAA, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 674 - 675)
    - Freshman results, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 676)
    - Varsity individual, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 677)
    - Varsity results, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 678)
    - EISL, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 679)
    - Indoor AAU, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 680 - 682)
    - Lake Erie Association Invitational for Women, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 682A)
    - Outdoor AAU (W), 1962 (Box 29, Folder 683)
    - Easterns, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 684)
    - Freshman results, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 685)
    - Varsity results, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 686)
    - Age groups, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 687)
    - Indoor AAU, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 688 - 689)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 690 - 691)
    - Indoor AAU (W), 1963 (Box 30, Folder 692)
    - Outdoor AAU (W), 1963 (Box 30, Folder 693)
    - Easterns, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 694)
    - AAU, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 695)
    - Easterns, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 696 - 697)
    - NCAA Championships, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 698)
    - Westerns, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 699)
    - Freshman splits, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 700)
    - Varsity splits, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 701)
    - Indoor AAU, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 702 - 703)
    - Indoor AAU (M), 1964 (Box 30, Folder 704)
    - Indoor AAU (W), 1964 (Box 30, Folder 705)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 706)
    - Easterns, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 707 - 708)
    - NCAA, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 709 - 710)
    - Freshman results, 1964-1965 (Box 30, Folder 711)
    - Varsity results, 1964-1965 (Box 30, Folder 712)
    - ESISC, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 713)
    - Indoor AAU, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 714)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 715)
    - ESIS, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 716 - 717)
    - NCAA, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 718 - 719)
    - Swim meets (Colgate, Dartmouth, Princeton), 1965 (Box 30, Folder 720)
    - Maccabiah games, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 721)
    - Indoor AAU, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 722 - 723)
    - Outdoor AAU, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 724)
    - Freshman results, 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 725)
    - Results, 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 726)
    - Easterns, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 727)
    - NCAA Championships, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 728 - 729)
    - Freshman results, 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 730)
    - AAU meets, 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 731)
    - Varsity results, 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 732)
    - Top 10 men's swimming times, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 733)
    - Short course AAU, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 734 - 735)
    - Easterns, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 736)
    - EISL, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 737)
    - Results, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 738)
    - Freshman results, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 739)
    - Freshman meets, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 740)
    - Varsity meets, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 741)
    - AAU, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 742)
    - ESIS Championships, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 743)
    - Results, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 744)
    - Prep school/high school meets, 1968-1971 (Box 31, Folder 745)
    - NCAAs, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 746)
    - Freshman results, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 747)
    - Varsity results, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 748)
    - AAU, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 749 - 751)
    - Easterns, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 752)
    - ESIS, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 753)
    - NCAA, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 754)
    - ESIS CHPS, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 755)
    - Results, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 756)
    - Freshman results, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 757)
    - Varsity results, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 758)
    - Results and splits, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 759)
    - AAU, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 760)
    - Easterns, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 761)
    - Results, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 762 - 763)
    - Freshman results, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 764)
    - Easterns, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 765)
    - Easterns, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 766)
    - Results, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 767 - 768)
    - AAU, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 769)
    - Easterns, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 770)
    - Best performance class of 1971, 1967-1971 (Box 32, Folder 771)
    - Results, 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 772)
    - Best performances class of 1972 (M), 1968-1972 (Box 32, Folder 773)
    - EISL, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 774 - 775)
    - AAU, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 776 - 777)
    - Results, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 778)
    - Triangular meet, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 779)
    - Results, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 780)
    - EISL, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 781)
    - EISL, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 782)
    - Easterns, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 783)
    - NCAA, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 784)
    - Ivy League champs, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 785)
    - Results (M), 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 786)
    - Results (W), 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 787)
    - Best Times, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 788)
    - Results, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 789)
    - Splits, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 790)
    - Results (M), 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 791)
    - Results (W), 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 792)
    - Splits (M), 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 793)
    - Splits (W), 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 794)
    - Results (M), 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 795)
    - Results (W), 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 796)
    - Results (W), 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 797)
    - Results (M), 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 798)
    - Results (W), 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 799)
    - Results (M), 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 800)
    - Results (W), 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 801)
    - Results, undated (Box 32, Folder 802 - 803)
    - Performance statistics, 1933-1957 (Box 33, Folder 804 - 815)
  - Scrapbooks
    - Yale note book, undated (Box 34, Folder 816)
    - The National Notebook, undated (Box 34, Folder 817)
    - Photographs, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 818)
    - Japan/USA AAU meet scrapbook, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 819)
  - Water Polo
    - 1956-1966 (Box 35, Folder 820)
    - 1961-1970 (Box 35, Folder 821)
    - 1968-1971 (Box 35, Folder 822)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 824)
    - Season wrap up, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 825)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 826)
- Records documenting swimming, 1905-2013; Accession 2013-A-039
  - Athlete files
    - Men
    - Women
  - Organization files
    - Men's Team
      - History and notes, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 779)
      - Swim records, 1946-1949 (Box 22, Folder 780)
      - Eastern Intercollegiate Swimming and Water Polo League, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 781)
      - NCAA championships results, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 782)
      - Correspondence and notes, 1902-1942 (Box 22, Folder 783)
      - Physical Education Library-summaries, statistics and reports, 1925-1939 (Box 22, Folder 784)
      - History-summaries and reports, 1923-1941 (Box 22, Folder 785)
      - Federation Internationale de Nation Amateur (FINA) correspondence and guidelines, 1937-1938 (Box 22, Folder 786)
      - Records, correspondence and notes, 1936-1968 (Box 22, Folder 787)
      - History, records, notes and rosters, 1905-1985 (Box 22, Folder 788)
      - History and miscellaneous, 1920-1921 (Box 22, Folder 789)
      - Photographs, 1930-1968 (Box 22, Folder 790)
      - Team photograph descriptions, 1898-1991 (Box 23, Folder 791)
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 23, Folder 792)
      - Competition photographs, 1950-1970 (Box 23, Folder 793-794)
      - Photographs-competitions, Olympics and meets, 1950-1960 (Box 23, Folder 795)
      - Photograph collage, 1898-1899 (Box 23, Folder 796)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1899 (Box 23, Folder 797)
      - Photographs and newsletters, 1900-1909 (Box 23, Folder 798)
      - Photographs and news bulletin (FINA), 1906-1907 (Box 23, Folder 799)
      - Photographs and team history, 1909-1910 (Box 23, Folder 800)
      - Statistics, records and photographs, 1913-1914 (Box 23, Folder 801)
      - Team history and photographs, 1918-1919 (Box 23, Folder 802)
      - Photographs, team history and correspondence, 1919-1920 (Box 23, Folder 803)
      - Pamphlets, reports and statistics, 1920-1921 (Box 23, Folder 804)
      - Photographs, reports, statistics and pamphlets, 1921-1922 (Box 23, Folder 805)
      - Pamphlets, reports, statistics and correspondence, 1922-1923 (Box 23, Folder 806)
      - Historical reports and correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 24, Folder 807)
      - Historical reports and photograph, 1924-1925 (Box 24, Folder 808)
      - Pamphlets, summaries, reports and programs, 1925-1926 (Box 24, Folder 809)
      - Pamphlets, summaries, reports and histories, 1926-1927 (Box 24, Folder 810)
      - Pamphlets, histories, notes and programs, 1927-1928 (Box 24, Folder 811)
      - History, notes, statistics and correspondence, 1928-1929 (Box 24, Folder 812)
      - Pamphlets, photographs, history and correspondence, 1929-1930 (Box 24, Folder 813)
      - Pamphlets, summaries, correspondence, statistics, 1929-1930 (Box 24, Folder 814)
      - Photographs, history and correspondence, 1930-1931 (Box 24, Folder 815)
      - History, pamphlets, statistics and correspondence, 1930-1931 (Box 24, Folder 816)
      - Photographs, pamphlets and notes, 1931-1932 (Box 24, Folder 817)
      - Pamphlets, correspondence, statistics and schedules, 1931-1932 (Box 24, Folder 818)
      - Schedules, pamphlets and descriptions, 1932-1933 (Box 25, Folder 819)
      - Schedules, rosters and reports, 1932-1933 (Box 25, Folder 820)
      - Photographs, pamphlets, schedules and reports, 1933-1934 (Box 25, Folder 821)
      - NCAA championships-split times, 1933-1934 (Box 25, Folder 822)
      - Pamphlets, statistics, rosters and schedules, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 823)
      - Pamphlets, statistics and summaries, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 824)
      - Eastern Intercollegiate Swimming League (EISL), 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 825)
      - Photographs, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 826)
      - Pamphlets, photographs and statistics, 1935-1936 (Box 25, Folder 827)
      - Programs, schedules, rosters and summaries, 1935-1936 (Box 25, Folder 828)
      - Correspondence, reports, pamphlets and statistics, 1936-1937 (Box 25, Folder 829)
      - Notes, rosters, statistics and National Amateur Athletic Union Championships (AAU), 1936-1937 (Box 25, Folder 830)
      - Photographs, pamphlets, reports, rosters and statistics, 1937-1938 (Box 25, Folder 831)
      - Summaries, reports and notes, 1937-1938 (Box 25, Folder 832)
      - National Collegiate A. A. Championships-Rutgers March 1938, 1937-1938 (Box 25, Folder 833)
      - Photographs, pamphlets, correspondence and statistics, 1938-1939 (Box 26, Folder 834)
      - Pamphlets, reports and statistics, 1938-1939 (Box 26, Folder 835)
      - Reports, statistics and notes, 1938-1939 (Box 26, Folder 836)
      - Photographs, pamphlets and forms, 1938-1939 (Box 26, Folder 837)
      - Photographs, pamphlets, statistics and rosters, 1939-1940 (Box 26, Folder 838)
      - Rosters and statistics, 1939-1940 (Box 26, Folder 839)
      - Statistics, rosters and notes, 1939-1940 (Box 26, Folder 840)
      - Statistics, reports and summaries, 1939-1940 (Box 26, Folder 841)
      - Pamphlets, statistics, reports and summaries, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 842)
      - Notes, history, statistics and reports, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 843)
      - Pamphlets, statistics, schedules and reports, 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 844)
      - Reports, summaries and statistics, 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 845)
      - Pamphlets, summaries and correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 846)
      - National Collegiate Swimming Championships, 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 847)
      - Photographs, 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 848)
      - Photographs, pamphlets, reports and statistics, 1942-1943 (Box 27, Folder 849)
      - Statistics, summaries and reports, 1942-1943 (Box 27, Folder 850)
      - Photographs, reports and statistics, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 851)
      - Statistics, reports and summaries, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 852)
      - Reports, summaries and statistics, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 853)
      - Results-winter season, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 854)
      - Notes, correspondence, event schedules and pamphlets, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 855)
      - Exhibition Pool, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 856)
      - Reports and correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 857)
      - Pamphlets and entry forms, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 858)
      - Pamphlets, reports and statistics, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 859)
      - Pamphlets and information forms, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 860)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 861)
      - Photographs, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 862)
      - Photographs and pamphlets, 1947-1948 (Box 29, Folder 863)
      - Pamphlets and newspaper clippings, 1947-1948 (Box 29, Folder 864)
      - Pamphlets, rosters, summaries and statistics, 1947-1948 (Box 29, Folder 865)
      - Freshman swimming, 1947-1948 (Box 29, Folder 866)
      - Varsity swimming, 1947-1948 (Box 29, Folder 867)
      - Los Angeles AAU Championships, 1948-1949 (Box 29, Folder 868)
      - Varsity swimming, 1948-1949 (Box 29, Folder 869)
      - Varsity swimming-information sheets, 1948-1949 (Box 29, Folder 870)
      - Correspondence and newspaper clippings, 1948-1949 (Box 29, Folder 871)
      - Pamphlets, programs, summaries and statistics, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 872)
      - Record attempts, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 873)
      - Varsity swimming, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 874)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 875)
      - Summaries, statistics, reports and pamphlets, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 876)
      - Information sheets, statistics and reports, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 877)
      - Pamphlets and newspaper clippings, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 878)
      - Photographs and record certificates, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 879)
      - Reports and statistics, 1950-1951 (Box 30, Folder 880)
      - Pamphlets and statistics, 1950-1951 (Box 30, Folder 881)
      - Pamphlets and newsletters, 1950-1951 (Box 30, Folder 882)
      - AAU Columbus OH, 1950-1951 (Box 30, Folder 883)
      - Varsity swimming results, 1950-1951 (Box 30, Folder 884)
      - Reports, statistics and pamphlets, 1950-1951 (Box 30, Folder 885)
      - Photographs, 1950-1951 (Box 31, Folder 886)
      - Photographs and statistics, 1951-1952 (Box 31, Folder 887)
      - Pamphlets, 1951-1952 (Box 31, Folder 888)
      - Varsity swimming, 1951-1952 (Box 31, Folder 889)
      - Roster, statistics and pamphlet, 1951-1952 (Box 31, Folder 890)
      - Pamphlets, statistics and reports, 1951-1952 (Box 31, Folder 891)
      - Information sheets, 1951-1952 (Box 31, Folder 892)
      - Photographs, 1952-1953 (Box 31, Folder 893)
      - Reports and statistics, 1952-1953 (Box 31, Folder 894)
      - Statistics, 1952-1953 (Box 31, Folder 895)
      - Information sheets, 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 896)
      - Pamphlets and reports on record times, 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 897)
      - Pamphlets and statistics, 1953-1954 (Box 32, Folder 898)
      - Varsity swimming, 1953-1954 (Box 32, Folder 899)
      - Photographs, 1953-1954 (Box 32, Folder 900)
      - Newspapers, reports, statistics and photographs, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 901)
      - Information sheets, statistics and pamphlets, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 902)
      - Correspondence and statistics, 1955-1956 (Box 33, Folder 903)
      - Varsity swimming scorecards, 1955-1956 (Box 33, Folder 904)
      - Pamphlets, 1955-1956 (Box 33, Folder 905)
      - Statistics, 1955-1956 (Box 33, Folder 906)
      - Photographs, 1955-1956 (Box 33, Folder 907)
      - Pamphlets and summaries, 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 908)
      - Pamphlets and information sheets, 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 909)
      - Information sheets, 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 910)
      - Photographs, 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 911)
      - Pamphlets and newspaper clippings, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 912)
      - Information sheets, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 913)
      - Freshman swimming-information sheets, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 914)
      - Photographs, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 915)
      - Varsity swimming scores, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 916)
      - Freshman swimming, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 917)